Guide to the Carl E. Ladd papers,1932-1943
Ladd, Carl E. papers, 1932-1943
- Carl E. Ladd papers
  - New York State Holstein-Friesian Association., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - New York State Home Bureau Federation., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - J Miscellaneous., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - K Miscellaneous., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - L Miscellaneous., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 46)
    Creel, Cecil W.
  - Committee on Experiment Station Organization and Policy., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 47)
    Buchanon, R.E.
  - Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities, Committee on Extension Organization and Policy., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 48)
    Brigham, Reuben; Wilson, M.L.; National Defense Commission.
  - Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities, Committee on Relationships., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 49)
    Wilson, M.L.; Creel, Cecil W.; United States Dept. of Agriculture, Extension Service; Federal-State relations.
  - Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities, Committee on Relationships., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 50)
    Walton, T.O.; Wilson, M.L.; Byrd, H.C.; United States Dept. of Agriculture; Extension Service.
  - Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities Questionnaire on Agriculture in Relation to National Defense., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 51-52)
    United States Dept. of Agriculture, Committee on Relationships; National Defense Commission; National defense.
  - Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities, Executive Committee., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 53)
    Cooper, Thomas P.; Walton, T.O.; National defense.
  - M Miscellaneous., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Metropolitan Cooperative Milk Producers Bargaining Agency., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 55)
    Baldwin, Charles H.
  - T.E. Milliman., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 56)
    Milliman, Thomas E.; Devon Cattle; Fertilizer.
  - New York State Bankers Association., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 57)
    Guild, E.B.; New York State Bankers Association, Farm Credit School.
  - New York Seed Improvement Cooperative Association Inc., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 58)
    Noyes, Holton V.; Jones, Bruce P.
  - O Miscellaneous., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - P Miscellaneous., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 60)
  - R Miscellaneous., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 61)
  - S Miscellaneous., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 62)
    Sugden, J.J.
  - Sears Roebuck and Company., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 63)
    Sears Roebuck Agricultural Foundation.
  - T Miscellaneous., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 64)
  - Tennessee Valley Authority., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 65)
  - Tully Nursery., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 66)
  - U Miscellaneous., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 67)
  - V Miscellaneous., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 68)
  - W Miscellaneous., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 69)
    Wallace, Henry A.; Wagenblass, Edith P.; Associated Country Women of the World.
  - United States Weather Bureau., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 70)
  - WGY., 1940-41 (Box 20, Folder 71)
  - Cornell University Board of Trustees., 1941-42 (Box 20, Folder 72)
    Meigs, Robert B.; AGFU; Arnot Forest.
  - Council for New York State College of Agriculture and Agricultural Experiment Stations., 1941-42 (Box 20, Folder 73)
    New York State College of Agriculture, Agricultural College Council.
  - Appointments, Leaves, etc, Recommended to President Day., 1941-42 (Box 20, Folder 74)
    Day, Edmund Ezra; New York State College of Agriculture.
  - President's Office, Day, Edmund Ezra; School of Living; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Rural Sociology; Bailey Hortorium; New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1941-42 (Box 20, Folder 75)
  - Dean of University Faculty., 1941-42 (Box 20, Folder 76)
    Betten, Cornelius; United States Navy, V-1 Program.
  - Cornell University Attorney, Workmen's compensation., 1941-42 (Box 20, Folder 77)
  - Buildings and Grounds., 1941-42 (Box 20, Folder 78)
  - Cornell University Secretary., 1941-42 (Box 20, Folder 79)
  - Treasurer's Office., 1941-42 (Box 20, Folder 80)
    Trousdale, James B.
  - Assistant Treasurer., 1941-42 (Box 20, Folder 81)
  - Office of the Dean., 1941-42 (Box 20, Folder 82)
  - Current Problems in Agriculture, Agr. Econ. 152., 1941-42 (Box 20, Folder 83-84)
    New York State Agricultural Conservation Program Organization.
  - Economic Data., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Requisitions., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Agricultural Economics 152., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Agricultural Economics and Farm Management., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    Spencer, Leland; Rogalsky, George F.; Roosevelt, Franklin D.; Day, Edmund Ezra; Myers, William I.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Agricultural Economics and Farm Management; Milk Marketing; Price fixing.
  - Business Office., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Milk Costs Conference., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Agricultural Engineering., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Agronomy., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Animal Husbandry., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    Morrison, Frank B.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Animal Husbandry.
  - TVA - Agronomy Project., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    McAmis, J. Carl; Tennessee Valley Authority; Fertilizer; TVA Phosphate.
  - Bailey Hortorium., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    Bailey Palm Glade.
  - Botany., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    Knudson, Lewis; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Botany.
  - Dairy Industry., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    Knaysi, Georges; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Dairy Industry.
  - Entomology., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    Palm, Charles E.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Entomology.
  - Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Station., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    Guterman, Carl E.F.; TVA Phosphate.
  - New York State Agricultural Experiment Station., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    Parrott, Percival J.; Breed, Robert S.; Tressler, Donald K.; Nebel, Bernard R.; Hebel, Mabel R.; Meigs, Robert B.; Heinicke, Arthur J.; Dahlberg, Arthur C.; New York State Division of Standards and Purchase; Bankhead-Jones Act.
  - Extension Service., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    Wilson, M.L.; Taylor, Charles A.; Simons, Lloyd R.; Kelsey, Lincoln D.; United States Dept. of Agriculture, Extension Service; New York State Cooperative Extension Service; Victory gardens.
  - Extension., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    Simons. Lloyd R.; Adams, Bristow.
  - State Leaders., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    Wright, William J.; Flansburgh, Earl A.; Muckle, Leo A.; New York State Cooperative Extension Service; Droughts.
  - Floriculture and Ornamental Horticulture., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    MacDaniels, Laurence H.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Floriculture and Ornamental Horticulture.
  - Forestry., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    Cope, Joshua A.; Hosmer, Ralph S.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Forestry; Civilian Conservation Corps.
  - Library., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Plant Breeding., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Plant Breeding.
  - Plant Pathology., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Pomology, Heinicke, Arthur J.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Pomology., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Poultry Husbandry., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    Romanoff, Alexis L.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Poultry Husbandry; New York Poultry Improvement Cooperative.
  - Poultry Husbandry Headship., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    Rice, James E.; Bruckner, John H.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Poultry Husbandry.
  - Resident Instruction., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    King, Asa C.; Gibson, Anson W.; Taylor, Charles A.
  - Rural Education., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    Stewart, Rolland M.; Butterworth, Julian E.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Rural Education.
  - Rural Sociology Sanderson, Dwight; Exner, Max; Boynton, Mary Fuertes; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Rural Sociology., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Vegetable Crops., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    Thompson, Homer C.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Vegetable Crops.
  - Zoology., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    Butt, Frederick B.; Hamilton, William J.
  - Home Economics., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    Meek, Howard B.; Henry, Gertrude M.; Blanding, Sarah Gibson; Stocking, Harriet B.; New York State College of Home Economics.
  - Summer Session., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - School of Nutrition., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Committees., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Bailey Hall Reservations., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    Murrow, Edward R.
  - Arboretum Committee., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Budget., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Beef Cattle Experiment, Hector Area., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 40)
    Kelsey, Lincoln D.; Watson, Alvin C.; Morrison, Frank B.; Smith, Frank M.; United States Dept. of Agriculture, Soil Conservation Service; Beef cattle.
  - Proposed Institute of Climatology., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 41)
    Von Engeln, O.D.; Thornwaite, C. Warren.
  - Farm and Home Week, 1942., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 42)
    Lehman, Herbert H.; Roosevelt, Eleanor; Blanding, Sarah Gibson; Poletti, Charles.
  - Farm Machinery Repair Program., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 43)
    Simons, Lloyd R.; Shapley, Sanford R.; Farm labor shortage.
  - New York State Nutrition Committee., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 44)
    Gardiner, Elizabeth M.
  - Publications Committee., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Traveling Fellowships., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Governor Lehman, Thomas E. Dewey., 1941-43 (Box 21, Folder 47)
    Lehman, Herbert H.; Dewey, Thomas E.; Hart, Van B.; Poletti, Charles.
  - Lt. Governor Charles Poletti., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Education., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 49)
    Miller, J. Hillis; Wilson, Lewis A.; Day, Edmund Ezra; Musto, Helen; New York State Dept. of Education.
  - New York State Dept. of Education., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 50)
    Miller, J. Hillis; Stoddard, George D.
  - Budget Director., 1941-43 (Box 21, Folder 51)
    Bryan, J. Buckley; Burton, John E.; New York State Division of the Budget.
  - New York State Division of Commerce., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - Conservation., 1941 (Box 21, Folder 53)
    Osbome, Lithgow; New York State Dept. of Conservation; New York State Emergency Food Commission; New York State Dept. of Conservation, Division of Fish and Game; Rationing; Reforestation.
  - United States Dept. of Agriculture., 1941-43 (Box 21, Folder 54)
    Davis, Chester C.; Wickard, Claude R.; New York State Emergency Food Commission; Devon Cattle.
  - Office of Experiment Stations., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 55)
    Jardine, James T.; Guterman, Carl E.F.; United States Dept. of Agriculture, Office of Experiment Stations.
  - Extension Service., 1941-42 (Box 21, Folder 56)
    Wilson, M.L.; Morgenthau, Henry Jr.; Eisenhower, Milton S.; Brigham, Reuben; United States Dept. of Agriculture, Extension Service.
  - Director of Extension Service., 1941-43 (Box 21, Folder 57)
    Wilson, M.L.; Elmhirst, Leonard K.; United States Dept. of Agriculture, Extension Service; Food distribution.
  - Agriculture and Markets., 1942-43 (Box 21, Folder 58)
    DuMond, Chester C.; Noyes, Holton V.; New York State Dept. of Agriculture and Markets.
  - United States Dept. of Agriculture, Soil Conservation Service., 1942 (Box 21, Folder 59)
    Stafford, Irving B.
  - New York State Emergency Food Commission., 1942 (Box 21, Folder 60)
    Riford, Lloyd S.; Winding, Charles A.; Dewey, Thomas E.; Simons, Lloyd R.; New York State War Council; War Food Administration; Rationing; Victory gardens; Food shortage; Farm labor; Farm Machinery Repair Program.
  - Volunteer Land Corps, Inc., 1942 (Box 21, Folder 61)
    Lindheim, Irma L.
  - New York State War Council., 1942-43 (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
  - New York State War Council., 1942-43 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    Corcoran, Thomas L.J.
  - New York State War Council., 1942-43 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    Lehman, Herbert H.; Poletti, Charles.
  - New York State War Council., 1942-43 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - New York State War Council., 1942 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    Fox, Dixon Ryan; Poletti, Charles; Lehman, Herbert H.; Corcoran, Thomas L.J.; New York State Defense Council.
  - New York State War Council., 1942-43 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    Winding, Charles A.
  - New York State War Council., 1942-43 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    Blanding, Sarah Gibson; Waste Fat Program; Child care.
  - New York State War Council., 1942-43 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    Victory gardens; Job discrimination.
  - A Miscellaneous., 1941-42 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    Rockefeller, Nelson A.; Uniao Cultural Brasil - Estados Unidos.
  - New York State Agricultural Society., 1941-42 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    Kirkland, Leigh G.; Eastman, Perley M.
  - American Agriculturist., 1941-42 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - B Miscellaneous., 1941-42 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Buck, J. Lossing; Begun, Isidore; Communist Party USA.
  - Howard E. Babcock., 1941-42 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Babcock, Howard E.; Grange League Federation; Farmers' Union; Broadcasting.
  - C Miscellaneous., 1941-42 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - D Miscellaneous Donlon, Mary H.; Dean, Daniel., 1941-42 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Dartington Hall., 1941-42 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    Elmhirst, Leonard K.; Elmhirst, Dorothy; Roosevelt, Eleanor.
  - Dairymen's League Cooperative Association, Inc., 1941-42 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    Coulter, J.A.
  - United Youth for Defense., 1941-42 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    United Youth for Victory.
  - E Miscellaneous., 1941-42 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - F Miscellaneous., 1941-42 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    Farrand, Margaret K.
  - American Farm Bureau Federation., 1941-42 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - New York State Farm Bureau Federation., 1941-42 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    Foster, Edward S.; New York State Agricultural Defense Committee; Farm Machinery Repair Program; Farm labor.
  - Farm Foundation., 1941-42 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    Taylor, Henry C.
  - Free Farmers Inc., 1941-42 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    Rosenman, Samuel I.; Lewis, John L.
  - G Miscellaneous., 1941-42 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Grange League Federation., 1941-42 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    McLellan, F.A.; McConnell, James A.; Milliman, Thomas E.
  - General Motors - Cornell World Price Index., 1941-42 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    Tucker, Rufus S.
  - Guernsey Breeders' Cooperative, Inc., 1941-42 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    Brown, Henry M.; Spencer, Leland; Myers, William I.
  - H Miscellaneous., 1941-42 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    Hiscock, Frank H.
  - Ithaca Savings Bank., 1941-42 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - J Miscellaneous., 1941-42 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    Jones, Fred M.; Price fixing.
  - K Miscellaneous., 1941-42 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - L Miscellaneous., 1941-42 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities., 1941-42 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    Lloyd, W.A.; Rose, Flora; Creel, Cecil W.; Walton, T.O.; Wickard, Claude R.; Byrd, H.C.; Simons, Lloyd R.; United States Dept. of Agriculture, Bureau of Agricultural Economics; War Manpower Commission; United States Dept. of Agriculture, Extension Service; Agricultural legislation; Social Security Act.
  - M Miscellaneous., 1941-42 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    Mann, Albert R.; Markham, G. Emerson; Morgenthau, Henry Jr.
  - N Miscellaneous., 1941-42 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    Nutter, William S.
  - New York State Bankers Association., 1941-42 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - National Youth Administration., 1941-42 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    Hesley, Karl D.
  - P Miscellaneous., 1941-42 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - R Miscellaneous., 1941-42 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    Migrant labor.
  - S Miscellaneous., 1941-42 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - New York Seed Improvement Cooperative Association, Inc., 1941-42 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - T Miscellaneous., 1941-42 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - V Miscellaneous., 1941-42 (Box 23, Folder 36)
    Van Loon, Hendrik Willem; Van Wagenen, Jared Jr.
  - W Miscellaneous., 1941-42 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - XYZ Miscellaneous., 1941-42 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - President Day., 1942-43 (Box 23, Folder 39)
    Day, Edmund Ezra; World War II.
  - President Day, Letters of Recommendation., 1942-43 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Dean of University Faculty., 1942-43 (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Buildings and Grounds., 1942-43 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Purchasing Department., 1942-43 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Cornell University Treasurer., 1942-43 (Box 23, Folder 44)
    Rogalsky, George F.; Trousdale, James B.
  - Assistant Treasurer., 1942-43 (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Business Office., 1942-43 (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Requisitions., 1941-42 (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Office of the Dean., 1942-43 (Box 23, Folder 48)
    War Production Board.
  - Budget, 1943-44., 1942-43 (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - Clippings., 1942-43 (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - Agricultural Economics., 1942-43 (Box 23, Folder 51)
    Myers, William I.; Hart, Van B.; Spencer, Leland; Granducci, O.S.; Sexauer, Fred H.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Agricultural Economics; Kiplinger Washington Agency; Food production.
  - Agricultural Engineering., 1942-43 (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - Agronomy., 1942-43 (Box 23, Folder 53)
    Bradfield, Richard; Howe, Frank B.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Agronomy; Tennessee Valley Authority; Fertilizer.
  - Animal Husbandry., 1942-43 (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - Bailey Hortorium., 1942-43 (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - Entomology., 1942-43 (Box 23, Folder 56)
    Palm, Charles E.; Guterman, Carl E.F.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Entomology.
  - Botany., 1942-43 (Box 23, Folder 57)
  - Dairy Industry., 1942-43 (Box 23, Folder 58)
    Sherman, James M.; Rahn, Otto; Sharp, Paul F.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Dairy Industry; Milk marketing.
  - New York State Agricultural Experiment Station., 1942-43 (Box 23, Folder 59)
    Heinicke, Arthur J.; Breed, Robert S.; Pincus, Sol; Parrott, Percival J.; Nebel, Bernard R.; New York State Nurserymen's Association.
  - Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Station., 1942-43 (Box 23, Folder 60)
    Guterman, Carl E.F.; United States Weather Bureau; World War II.
  - New York State Cooperative Extension Service, Appointments, Resignations., 1942-43 (Box 23, Folder 61)
  - Extension Service., 1942-43 (Box 23, Folder 62)
    Simons, Lloyd R.; Adams, Bristow; United States Dept. of Agriculture, Extension Service; Farm labor.
  - Publications., 1942-43 (Box 23, Folder 63)
  - L.D. Kelsey., 1942-43 (Box 23, Folder 64)
    Kelsey, Lincoln D.; Near East Foundation; New York State Soil Conservation Service.
  - Phillips, Elmer S., 1942-43 (Box 23, Folder 65)
  - Taylor, Charles A., 1942-43 (Box 23, Folder 66)
    Advertising.
  - New York State Farm Bureau Federation., 1942-43 (Box 23, Folder 67)
    Morris, Fred B.; Flansburgh, Earl A.
  - Junior Extension., 1942-43 (Box 23, Folder 68)
    Hoefer, Albert; Four-H Clubs.
  - Robinson, Montgomery E., 1942-43 (Box 23, Folder 69)
  - Farm Practice., 1942-43 (Box 23, Folder 70)
  - Floriculture and Ornamental Horticulture., 1942-43 (Box 23, Folder 71)
  - Forestry., 1942-43 (Box 23, Folder 72)
    Cope, Joshua A.; Recknagel, A. Bernard; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Forestry; Arnot Forest.
  - Library., 1942-43 (Box 23, Folder 73)
  - Plant Breeding., 1942-43 (Box 23, Folder 74)
    Love, Harry H.; Guterman, Carl E.F.; Kung, H.H.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Plant Breeding.
  - Plant Pathology., 1942-43 (Box 23, Folder 75)
  - Pomology., 1942-43 (Box 23, Folder 76)
  - Poultry Husbandry., 1942-43 (Box 23, Folder 77)
    Bruckner, John H.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Poultry Husbandry.
  - Resident Instruction., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Gibson, Anson W.; Cornell University, Office of Resident Instruction; World War II.
  - Rural Education and Graduate School of Education., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    Gibson, Anson W.; Palmer, E. Laurence; Butterworth, Julian E.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Rural Education; Cornell University, School of Education; Air Service Command.
  - Rural Sociology., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    Sanderson, Dwight; Strode, Josephine; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Rural Sociology.
  - School of Nutrition., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    McCay, Clive M.; Maynard, Leonard A.; Cornell University, School of Nutrition; War Defense Council; State Bread Program.
  - Summer Session., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Vegetable Crops., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    Karoly, Thomas F.; Platenius, Hans; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Vegetable Crops.
  - Zoology., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    Hutt, Frederick B.; Hamilton, William J.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Zoology.
  - University Library., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Home Economics., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    Blanding, Sarah Gibson; Henry, Mary F.; New York State College of Home Economics; New York State Nursing Council for War Service; New York State Home Economics Association.
  - Hotel Administration., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    Meek, Howard B.; Cornell University, Dept. of Hotel Administration; Statler Hall.
  - Bailey Hall Reservations., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Budget, 1942-43., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Farm and Home Week., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    Kelsey, Lincoln D.; Dewey, Thomas E.
  - Correspondence Regarding Memoranda of Understanding., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    Morrison, Frank B.; New York Farmers, Inc.; New York State Soil Conservation Service.
  - Farm Labor., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    Shapley, Sanford R.; United States Dept. of Agriculture, Extension Service; New York State Agricultural Defense Committee; War Manpower Commission; New York State Farm Labor Program; Draft deferments.
  - Farm Machinery Repair Program., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous Committees., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Publications Committee., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Arboretum Committee., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Committee on Planning and Coordination, War Effort., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Wartime Committees, Extension., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    New York State Victory Garden Council.
  - Committee on Rubber Producing Plants., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    Geer, William C.; Guterman, Carl E.F.; Knudson, Lewis; B.F. Goodrich Company; National Farm Chemurgic Council.
  - A Miscellaneous., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - American Agriculturist., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    Eastman, Edward R.; Lewis, John L.; Dairy Farmers' Union; Unions.
  - New York State Agricultural Society., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - New York State Artificial Breeders Association., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Agricultural Missions, Inc., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    Reisner, John H.
  - Applications and Recommendations for Positions., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - B Miscellaneous., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    Beneway, Frank W.; Barnum, Jerome D.; Day, Edmund Ezra.
  - Babcock, Howard E., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    Kirkland, Leigh G.; Grange League Federation.
  - C Miscellaneous., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - New York State Conference Board of Farm Organizations., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    New York State Agricultural Defense Committee; Farm labor; Food production.
  - D Miscellaneous., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    Donlon, Mary H.; Dewey, Thomas E.; Blanding, Sarah Gibson; Farm labor.
  - Dartington Hall., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    Elmhirst, Leonard K.; Currie, John R.; Devon Cattle.
  - Dairymen's League Cooperative Association, Inc., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    Sexauer, Fred H.; Lindheim, Irma L.; Volunteer Land Corps, Inc.; Farm labor.
  - E Miscellaneous., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 36)